A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Accessions 1997-2008, Record Group 4 FA785
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2008:073, 1989-2006; 9; 38.11 Cubic Feet 28 standard record storage boxes, boxes 190-217.
  - Program Exploration, 5
    - Markle Foundation-Journalistic Standards - Edith Bjornson (D98330), 1998 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Markle Foundation-Internet Regulation - Zoe Baird (DJ99106), 1998 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Markle Foundation-Chinese Journalists Meeting - Zoe Baird (D99107), 1998 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Markle Foundation-PRI and New Models of Engagement - Barbara O'Keefe (DJ99111), 1998 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Markle Foundation- Program Exploration II - Zoe Baird (BJ99113), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Markle Foundation-Universal Access Project - Julia Moffett (DJ99112), 1998 (Box 195, Folder 11-12)
    - Harvard University - Winsten, Jay (DG99215), 1999 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Markle Foundation- Foundation Review - Julia Moffett (DJ99220), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Markle Foundation- Celinda Lake- Parent Focus Groups - Barbara O'Keefe (DJ99218), 1999 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Harvard University - Winsten, Jay (DG99215), 1999 (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Internet and the Minnesota Gubernational Race - Frank Luntz (DJ99224), 1998 (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Internews - Lorraine Dillon (DG99327), 1999 (Box 195, Folder 18)
  - Communications Policy, 6
    - Rutgers University - Jackie Hlavsa (D94105), 1993-1998 (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - Duke University - Ellen Mickiewicz (G94111), 1993-2000 (Box 196, Folder 1-3)
    - Duke University - Ellen Mickiewicz (G95326), 1995 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Telecommunications Policy Studies - Henry Geller (J96006), 1995-1998 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - London Business School - Patrick Barwise (G96109), 1996-1997 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - RAND Corporation - Dick Neu - Universal Email Research (G96328), 1996-1999 (Box 196, Folder 7-9)
    - The Aspen Institute - Charlie Firestone (G97107), 1996-1999 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - The Aspen Institute (G99222), 1999 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee (D98223), 1998 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Markle Foundation - Communications Technologies Studies - Murray (J9637) (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Duke University - Ellen Mickiewicz, 1996 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Duke University - Ellen Mickiewicz (G97108), 1996; Includes digital media. (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Carnegie Mellon University - Robert Kraut (G97109), 1997-1998 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - David Thorburn (G97225), 1997-2000 (Box 197, Folder 3-6)
    - The Brookings Institution - Robert Crandall (G97227), 1997-2000 (Box 197, Folder 7-9)
    - Columbia University - CITI - Eli Noam (G97229), 1997-1999 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Universal Access - Email - Lloyd Morrisett (J97336), 1997 (Box 197, Folder 11-13)
    - Oxford University - Monroe Price - Program in Comparative Media Law and Policy (G98004), 1997-1999 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Stanford University - Roger Noll - Economic Policy Research (G98006), 1997-2000 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Fordham University - Les Brown - Oral History of Television (D98108), 1997-1998 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundation-Mass Communications law in Contemporary China - Xia Yong (DJ98326), 1998 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Cardozo School of Law-Yeshiva University - Monroe Price (BJ98333), 1998 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Markle Foundation - IAG - E-Mail For All Campaign - Barbara O'Keefe (BJ98334), 1998-1999 (Box 198, Folder 6-7)
    - Connecticut Public TV and Radio - Franklin, Jerry (G98335), 1998 (Box 198, Folder 8-9)
    - Telecom. Policy Research Conf. - Baer, Walter (G98336), 1998-1999 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Center for Governmental Studies - Tracy Weston - DemocracyNext Strategic Plan (BG99108), 1998-1999 (Box 198, Folder 11-12)
    - Vanderbilt University - Hoffman, Donna - Digital Divide (DG993025), 1999-2001 (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - Interactive Media for Children, 7
    - University of Texas, Austin - Wright (G95217), 1995-1997 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - University of Massachusetts - Anderson (G97005), 1996-1999 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Public Broadcasting Archives - Davidson (972018), 1997-1999 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Harvard University - Edith Bjornson-Winsten, Jay (DJ98328), 1998-1999 (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Lake Snell Perry - Children's Program (DJ99218), 1999 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - Lake Snell Perry - Children's Program (DJ99218), 1999 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Markle Foundation - University of Texas at Austin - Wartella (993043BP), 1999-2000; Includes digital media. (Box 199, Folder 2-5)
    - WNET, New York - New York Online Learning Adventure, 1999 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Pencil, Inc. - Debbie Fife (001007DG), 1999 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Markle Foundation - Wartella - Barbara O'Keefe (001008DE), 1999-2000 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Ad Council - Peggy Conlon (001016BG), 1999-2000 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Markle Foundation - Kids Research Report - Alice Cahn (001017DP), 1999 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - David Stone - Kids Reserch Report (001017DP-A), 2000 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Kids Producer Metting - Markle Foundation - Zoe Baird (001018DP), 2000 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - MOUSE - Andrew Rasiej (001019DG), 1999 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Nancy Peretsman (001025DG), 2000 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Girls, Inc - Denise Roman (002030DG), 2000 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Children's Research Compendium (003043BP), 2000-2001 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Northwestern University - Barbara O'Keefe (003043BP-A), 2000-2001 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Skhema-Kratt - Beth Lind - Business Planning (003043BP-B), 2000 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Kratt Brothers - Martin Kratt (003043BP-C), 2000-2001 (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Children's Consultant - Ellen Wartella (003043BP-D), 2001 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Consulting Contract - Barbara O'Keefe (003043BP-E) (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Consulting Contract - Penelope Peterson (003043BP-F) (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - WBGH - Carol Greenwald (003043BP-G), Includes digital media. (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Grant Media, Inc. - Gretchen Grant (003043BP-H), 2001 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Sesame Workshop - Glenda Revelle (003043BP-I) (Box 200, Folder 6-7)
    - Kidsnet - Karen Jaffe (003043BP-J) (Box 200, Folder 8-10)
    - Children's Program- Applied Research- - Michael Cohen (003043BP-K), 2001 (Box 200, Folder 11-12)
    - Eduventures - Stokes (003043BP-M), 2001 (Box 200, Folder 13-15)
    - MOUSE - Sarah Halloway (11001), 2000 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Public Broadcasting Service - Pat Nugent (011005BP-A), 2001 (Box 200, Folder 17-19)
    - Discovery Communications, Inc. - Marjorie Kaplan (011005BP-B), 2001-2003 (Box 200, Folder 20-24)
    - TEDX Virtual Teacher - Jeffrey Nelson (011009DGC-A), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - The Gass Company, Inc. - Stephen Gass (012036DJ), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 2-3)
    - World Scholar Athlete Games - Alan Hassenfeld (013044DG), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - KIDSNET Lamb Chop Award - Karen Jaffe (013045DG), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - University of Chicago: Cultural Policy Program - Lawrence Rothfield (013046DG), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Explorations in Technology and Science - Douglas Rushkoff (013048DP), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Consumers Union - Rhoda Karpatkin (013050BG), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 8-9)
    - WBGH Educational Fund - Carol Greenwald (013051BG), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 10-14)
    - Near Life - Robot Garage (013052BP), 2001 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Fellowship - Linda Roberts (013053BP-A), 2001-2002 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Just Kid, Inc. - George Carrey (013053BP-D), and Environmental Scan Addendum (013053BP-D1), 2002 (Box 201, Folder 17-23)
    - Proteus Consulting - Susan Saltrick (013053BP-E), 2002 (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Global Nomads Group - Kamal El-Watter (021005) (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Michael Cohen Group LLC - Michael Cohen (013053BP-F), 2002 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - The Foundation for Accountability (FACT), 2002 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Yankelovich-Nickelodeon Yankelovich Youth Monitor Forum - Marjorie Goldstein (013059DP), 2000-2001 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Burness Communications, 2001 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Tara Sonenshine (013062BPC-D), 2001 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Internet Archive - Brewster Kahle (021005DG), 2001 (Box 202, Folder 7-8)
    - MOUSE - Sarah Halloway (021009DG), 2001 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - GlobeKids, Inc. - Khalid Quadir (023021DP), 2002; Includes digital media. (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Classroom, Inc. - Madeline Lacovara (023022DG), 2002 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Global Kids (Media Cares) - Carole Artigiani (Contribution: No #), 2001 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Center for Communications - Catherine Williams (31010DG), 2002 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Parks and History - Reginald Hagood (031016DG), 2002-2003 (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - MOUSE - Carole Wacey (041003DG), 2003 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - MOUSE - Carole Wacey (043009DG), 2004 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - TED X 2000 - Virtual Teacher Challenge - Tim Rowe (Box 202, Folder 17-21)
  - Miscellaneous, 8
    - Columbia University, CITI - Noam, Eli (G98338), 1998 (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - Markle Foundation - Website - (J98339), 1998 (Box 202, Folder 23)
    - Markle Foundation - Social Venture Capital Book (D98216), 1997-1998 (Box 202, Folder 24)
    - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Peter Swords (DG99219), 1999 (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - Independent Sector - Sara Melendez (DG99221), 1999 (Box 202, Folder 26)
    - National Center for Missing and Exploited Children - Ernie Allen (DG99326), 1999; Includes digital media. (Box 202, Folder 27)
    - Catalyst - Wellington, Sheila (DG99328), 1999 (Box 202, Folder 28)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts - Marc Weiss (DG99330), 1999 (Box 202, Folder 29)
    - The Foundation Center - Sara Engelhardt (DG99331), 1999 (Box 202, Folder 30)
    - International Advisory Group - J. Zemmol (DJ99336), 1999-2000 (Box 202, Folder 31)
    - International Rescue Committee - Paul Meyer (DG99337), 1999-2000 (Box 202, Folder 32)
    - Public Affairs Program - Julia Moffett (993045BP), 1999 (Box 202, Folder 33)
    - Mae Griffin - Karen Byers (993046BP), 1999-2000 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - International Program Exploration - Robert Davidson (000106DE), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Markle Foundation - Julia Moffett - Doug Rushkoff (000214DE-A), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundation-International Program Exploration Reallocation - Julia Moffett (000215DE), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Link - Stanford University - Smita Singh (001003DG), 1999-2000 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Catalyst - Wellington, Sheila (001006DG), 1999-2000 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists - Lucy M. Harrop (001009DG), 1998 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Council on Foundations - Dorothy Ridings (001021DG), 1999 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Catalyst - Wellington, Sheila (001023DG), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Markle Foundation-Exploration of Digital Art - Julia Moffett (001027DP), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - International Rescue Committee - Paul Meyer, Julia Moffett (001028DG), 2000-2002 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - International Rescue Committee - Julia Moffett (001028DP), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - New York University- National Center on Philanthropy the Law at NYU School - Harvey Dale (002032DG), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Markle Foundation- Digital Based Art - Zoe Baird (002034DP), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Creative Time, Inc. - Digital Art Group - Elizabeth Iapprino (002035DG), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Jon Small (002040DG), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Markle Foundation - Public Affairs Program - A. Wolfcale (003045BP), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Markle Foundation - Public Affairs Program -President's Letter - Michele Nix (003045BP-A), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - Mae Griffin - Stipend (003046BP), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women - Beijing Plus 5 - Promita Sengupta (003048DG), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - University of Texas Press - Bruce Buchanan, 2000 (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - University of Texas at Austin - Dr. Ellen Wartella, 1999 (Box 203, Folder 22)
    - Center for Democracy and Technology - Internews (003049DG), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 23)
    - RAND Corporation - Web Projects - Mitchell Wade (00203206), 1999 (Box 203, Folder 24)
    - Markle Foundation - Website Redesign (Box 203, Folder 25-29)
    - NYRAG - Barbara Bryan (011002DG), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 30)
    - Independent Sector - Sara Melendez (011003DG), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 31)
    - Digital Art Project - Carl Goodman (011008BP-A), 2000-2002 (Box 203, Folder 32)
    - Digital Art Project - Mark Napier (011008BP-B), 2002 (Box 203, Folder 33)
    - The Foundation Center - Sara Engelhardt (011012DG), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 34)
    - Catalyst - Sheila Wellington (012032DG), 2000-2001 (Box 203, Folder 35)
    - The Foundation Center - Sara Engelhardt (012037DG), 2000 (Box 203, Folder 36)
    - Council on Foundation - Dorothy S. Ridings (012038DG), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 37)
    - Independent Sector - Sara Melendez (012039DG), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 38)
    - The Foundation Center - Sara Engelhardt (012041DG), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 39)
    - Livingston-Moffett Consulting - Livingston (013057BP), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 40)
    - Markle Annual Membership - Mae Griffin (013060BP), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 41)
    - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Jon Small (013060BP-B), 2000-2002 (Box 203, Folder 42)
    - New York Regional Association of Grant Makers - Barbara Bryan (013060BP-C), 2001-2002 (Box 203, Folder 43)
    - Council on Foundations - Dorothy Ridings (013060BP-D), 2002 (Box 203, Folder 44)
    - Independent Sector - Sara Melendez (013060BP-E), 2002 (Box 203, Folder 45)
    - Columbia University School of Law - David Leebron (013060BP-F), 2002 (Box 203, Folder 46)
    - New York Regional Association of Grant Makers - Barbara Bryan (013060BP-G), 2002-2003 (Box 203, Folder 47)
    - The Foundation Center - Sara Engelhardt (013060BP-H), 2002 (Box 203, Folder 48)
    - The Julliard School - Simone Wicha (013060BP-I), 2002-2003 (Box 203, Folder 49)
    - John Glassie (013062BPC-A), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 50)
    - Todd McGovern (013062BPC-B), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 51)
    - Hill and Knowlton - Michael Gordon (013062BPC-E), 2002 (Box 203, Folder 52)
    - International Women's Foundation - Sherry Rocky (021004DG), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 53)
    - United Way - September 11th Fund - Kim Kayser (021007DG), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 54)
    - Ms Magazine-Feminist Majority Foundation - Marcia Gillespie (022014DG), 2001 (Box 203, Folder 55)
    - Robinson Lerer and Montgomery - Fischer, 2001 (Box 203, Folder 56)
    - Markle Fellow - Douglas Rushkoff (022018DG), 2001-2002 (Box 204, Folder 1-2)
    - International Center for Research on Women - Dr Geeta Rao Gupta (022020DG), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - The Unusual Suspects Theatre Company - Laura Leigh Hughes (023024DG), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Internoded - Chug Perry (023027BP-P), 2003-2004 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Jon Small (023028BP-B), 2002-2003 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Council on Foundations - Dorothy Ridings (023028BP-C), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Council on Foundations - Sara Engelhardt (023028BP-E), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Mae Griffin Family - Mae Griffin (023028BP-F), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - NYRAG - Michael Seltzer (023028BP-G), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Jon Small (023028BP-H), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Independent Sector - Marianne Eby (023028BP-I), 2004-2005 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - NY Regional Association of Grant Makers - Michael Seltzer (023028BP-J), 2004-2005 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Jon Small (023028BP-K), 2003-2004 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Education Fund - Antonia Hernandez (023032DG), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Independent Sector - Sara Melendez (023028BP-D), 2001-2003 (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists - Thomas Glocer (031002DG), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - International Women's Media Foundation - Judy Woodruff (031003DG), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Digital Age Productions - Shapiro (031912DP), 2002; Includes digital media. (Box 204, Folder 19)
    - The Links - Connie Hubbard (031012DP), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 20)
    - Lawyer's Committee for Human Rights - Michael Posner (041002DG), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 21)
    - Freedom's Answer - Doug Bailey (041004DG), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - Council on Foundations - Dorothy Ridings (042001DG), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 23)
    - Public Agenda - Daniel Yankelovich (042005DG), 2003 (Box 204, Folder 24)
  - Opportunity Fund - Digital Divide, 9
    - Tisch School of the Arts at New York University - George Agudow (002039DG), 2000-2001 (Box 204, Folder 25)
    - Council for Excellence in Government - Joiwind Ronen (011006BP-A), 2001 (Box 204, Folder 26)
    - Center for Democracy and Technology - George Sadowsky (011006BP-B), 2002-2003 (Box 204, Folder 27-28)
    - Council for Excellence in Government - Palemo Roundtable (011006BP-D), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 29)
    - SwandiveDigital - Brian Reisinger (011006BP-E), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 30)
    - Interaction American Council for Voluntary International Action - Kenneth Giunta (011006BP-J), 2002 (Box 204, Folder 31)
    - The Council for Excellence in Government - Joiwind Ronen (011014BP-A), 2001 (Box 204, Folder 32)
    - The Benton Foundation - Larry Kerkman (011014BP-B), 2001-2002 (Box 204, Folder 33)
    - Educational Development Center - Janice Brodman (011014BP-D), 2001 (Box 204, Folder 34)
    - United Nations Development Programme - Henry Jackelen (011014BP-E), 2001 (Box 204, Folder 35)
    - United Nations ICT Advisory - Julia Moffett (011015BP), 2000-2002 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Opportunity Initiative - Julia Moffett (011016BP), 2000-2002 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Claudia Frittelli (011017BPC-A), 2001 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Fred Tipson (011017BPC-B), 2001-2002 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - The Center for Democracy and Technology- Internews (GIPI) - Jim Dempsey (011018BP-A), 2000-2001 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - University of California, San Diego - Peter Cowhey (011019BP-A), 2001 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Voxiva, LLC - Paul Meyer (011019BP-B), 2001 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - World Resources Institute - Al Hammond (011020BPC-A), 2001 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - World Resources Institute - Al Hammond (011020BPC-B), 2001-2002 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Chang H. Suh (011020BP-C), 2002; Includes digital media. (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - World Resources Institute - Al Hammond (011022BP), 2001 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - World Resources Institute - Al Hammond (011023BP), 2001-2002 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - World Resources Institute - Al Hammond (021011BP-G), 2002-2003 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - University of Maryland - Ernest Wilson (011024BP), 2001-2003 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - GDOI Team RSA Travel - Julia Moffett (021011BP-A), 2002 (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Bridges.org - Teresa Peters (021011BP-B), 2002 (Box 205, Folder 16-17)
    - Public Interest Projects - Pamela Maurath (021011BP-C), 2002 (Box 205, Folder 18-19)
    - University of California, San Diego - Peter Cowhey (021011BP-D), 2002 (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - United Nations Development Program-UNDP - Carlos Lopes (021011BP-E), 2002 (Box 205, Folder 21)
    - United Nations ICT Task Force (UN ICT) - Sarbuland Khan (021011BP-F), 2002 (Box 205, Folder 22-23)
    - United Nations ICT Task Force (UN ICT) - Sarbuland Khan (021011BP-F), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service-NYU - Dennis Smith (021011BP-H), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - United Nations Development Program-UNDP - Stephen Browne (021011BP-I), 2003 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Brookings Institution - James Steinberg (021012BP-B), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Dan Rosen - Dan Rosen (021012BP-C), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - McConnell International - Bruce McConnell (021012BP-D), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Thomas Kalil - Thomas Kalil (021012BP-E), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - World Resources Institute (WRI) - Allen Hammond (021012BP-F), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Children's Partnership - Laurie Lipper (002031BP-B), 2000-2001 (Box 206, Folder 9-10)
    - Leadership Conference Reports - Karen McGill Lawson (002031BP-D), 2000-2002 (Box 206, Folder 11-14)
    - Benton Foundation - Tony Wilhelm (002031BP-E), 2000-2001 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - National Indian Telecommunications Institute - Karen Buller (002031BP-F), 2000 (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - Princeton University - Stanley Katz (002031BP-G), 2000-2004 (Box 206, Folder 17-18)
    - Fund for the City of NY - Mary McCormick (002031BP-H), 2001 (Box 206, Folder 19-20)
    - Digital Divide (002031BP), 2000-2003 (Box 207, Folder 1-3)
    - One Economy Corporation - Ben Hecht (013061BP-A), 2000-2001 (Box 207, Folder 4-6)
    - The Children's Partnership - Laurie Lipper (013061BP-B), 2001-2002 (Box 207, Folder 7-8)
    - Educational Netcasting Foundation - Henry Gates (013061BP-C), 2001-2002; Includes digital media. (Box 207, Folder 9-12)
    - Bay Area Video Coalition - Kris Palmer (013061BP-D), 2001-2002; Includes digital media. (Box 207, Folder 13-14)
    - University of California, San Diego - Morgan Hunter (021003DG), 2001 (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences - Guo Liang (023026DG), 2002-2003 (Box 207, Folder 16-17)
    - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences - Guo Liang (023026DG), 2002-2003 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - USIA - Julia Moffett (DJ993029), 1999 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Lead the Future-Julia Moffett - Julia Moffett (993044BP), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - New America Foundation - Ted Halstead (001014BG), 1999; Includes digital media. (Box 208, Folder 4-6)
    - New America Foundation - Fellows (Box 208, Folder 7-17)
    - Greenberg Quinlan Research - Joseph Goode (002028BP-A), 2000 (Box 208, Folder 18-27)
    - Mindbeam, LLC - Greg Simon (002028BP-B), 2000 (Box 208, Folder 28)
    - Consulting Contract - Karen Kornbluh (002028BP-C), 2001 (Box 208, Folder 29)
    - International Rescue Committee - Paul Meyer (001024DG), 1999-2000 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Rhode Island School of Design - Roger Mandle (011007BP), 2001-2003; Includes digital media. (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Rock the Vote Education Fund - Mario Velasquez (012040DG), 2001 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - China: Internet Related Products - Nina Hachigian (PEJ0214), 2001 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - New America Foundation - Gordon Silverstein (020013PG), 2001-2002 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Digital Age - Andrew Shapiro (021001DP), 2001 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Internews Networks - David Hoffman (023023DG), 2002 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - The Syngergos Institute - Jim Brasher (031015DG), 2002 (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund - Antonia Hernandez (001020DG), 1999 (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Center for War, Peace and the News Media- New York University - Drazen Pantic (002037DG), 2000 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Interactive Communications Technology, 10
    - Boston University - Lee Sproull (G94332), 1994 (Box 208, Folder 30-31)
    - Markle Foundation-Online Comm. Research - Sandberg-Diment (D95216), 1995-1998 (Box 208, Folder 32)
    - Markle Foundation - Empirical Analysis - Andrew Ehrenberg (D97332), 1997-1999 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - California Institute of Tech. - Murray, Bruce (G97337), 1997 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Web White and Blue (WWB), 11